Guide to the Lambda Alpha International, Philadelphia Chapter Records, 1968-1988
Lambda Alpha International Philadelphia Chapter Records, 1968-1988
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Lambda Alpha International, Philadelphia Chapter, Records, 1968-1988
3593
Lambda Alpha International. Philadelphia Chapter.
1.5 cubic ft.
Minutes, member notices, and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes, member notices, and correspondence. Part of Lambda Alpha Literary Archives.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes, member notices, and correspondence. Part of Lambda Alpha Literary Archives.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Lambda Alpha International. Philadelphia Chapter.
Subjects:
Land use--Economic aspects.; Land economics.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, minutes and member notices, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Financial statements, fraternity agendas, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Past meetings, minutes, journal articles, 1968-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Constitution and by-laws, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes of meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "Keynotes" newsletter, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- "Keynotes" Scribe and Journal representative, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Membership proposals, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Member notices and correspondence, Jan.-July 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Member notices, minutes, notes, Aug.-Sept. 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Budgets, member notices, correspondence, Oct.-Dec. 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Meeting attendance, elections, membership dues, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- San Francisco mortgages, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Ritual for induction, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Individual member applications, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Correspondence of Paul A. Wilhelm, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Individual member applications, Jan.-April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Individual member applications, May-Dec. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Constitution and by-laws, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Correspondence, minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Annual Forecasting Meetings, The Racquet Club of Philadelphia, Dec. 1980-Jan. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Board meeting, The Racquet Club of Philadelphia, June 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Board meeting, The Racquet Club of Philadelphia, July 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Board meeting, The Racquet Club of Philadelphia, Oct.-Dec. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Board meeting, The Racquet Club, Sept.-Oct. 1980, Jan. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Board meeting, The Racquet Club, April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Board meeting, The Racquet Club, July 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Board meeting, The Racquet Club, Dec. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Members' meeting, New Franklin Plaza, Sept. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Members' meeting, The Racquet Club, Oct.-Nov. 1980, Feb. 1981, Nov. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Members' meeting, The Racquet Club, June 1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Charles H. Dager, Secretary, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Members' monthly meetings, Feb.-June 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Marc Brookman, Chairman, Service Committee-Expansion, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Leslie J. Carson, Jr. Treasurer, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Charles W. Harvey, Jr., V.P. for Administration, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- William L. Kaplan, V.P. for International Affairs, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Thomas J. Maher, V.P. for Program and Education, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Alfred R. Marcks, Jr., Chairman, By-Laws Committee, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- David C. Melnicoff, Chairman, Forecast Committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Lennox L. Moak, Public Relations Scribe, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Felice A. Rocca, Chairman, Membership Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Joseph Strauss, Jr., Chairman, Program Committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Susan M. Wachter, L.A. Archivist and Historian, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Paul A. Wilhelm, Chairman, Nominating Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Racquet Club accounts, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous correspondence and memos, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- New memberships and nominations, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Fraternity business and organizational concerns. Also, 50th Anniversary of the Biennial Congress, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Individual member applications, Jan.-Dec. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Minutes of Philadelphia Chapter meetings, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Minutes of Philadelphia Chapter meetings, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Minutes of Philadelphia Chapter meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Minutes of Philadelphia Chapter meetings, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Minutes of Philadelphia Chapter meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Membership directory of the George Washington Chapter, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Luncheon information and guest speakers, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Guide to the Lambda Alpha Papers at Cornell, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Typescript manuscript on neighborhood conditions and how they relate to city and metropolitan conditions, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 20)